ilait.com 2019-05-05

# Data Processing Agreement - Ilait

This Privacy Policy ("PP") is incorporated by reference in ilait Partner Agreement: Terms of Service (the "Agreement") and may apply to relations with End Customers through an ilait Partner where Agreement is in effect. Capitalized terms used in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning given in the Agreement. Direct all inquiries concerning this Privacy Policy to privacy@ilait.com.

## 1\. Automated Data Collection

When you visit www.ilait.com or partner.ilait.com we will use Google Analytics to collect the following information about your visit;

  * what browser and version you’re currently using
  * what language you’ve configured in your browser
  * if you can to us from any other site (referrer)
  * the links you click while on any of our sites
  * your IP address and country of origin

We use the above collected information to assist us in;

  * understanding what browser capabilities, you’re using so that we can improve your experience when visiting us
  * evaluate what services you and other people are interested in when visiting us
  * providing and improving your ability to manage services through our control panel
  * offering you fast and reliable help through our support channels in our control panel
  * monitor usage and activity of different management components in our control panel

We do not use any automatically collected information to learn about you personally and will not sell nor share the above information with any other parties than those described in this Privacy Policy.

## 2\. Cookies and Log Files

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We use cookies only to keep track of your logged in session at ilait Control Panel (partner.ilait.com). We also use Google Analytics as described in Section 1 which generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our sites are used to create reports about the use of the sites. Google will store this information, see [Google Analytics Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html) for more information.

All access to www.ilait.com and partner.ilait.com will also be logged in our systems. We do that primarily to be able to investigate abnormal behaviors in usage patterns and proactively mitigate different kind of attacks and thereby improve your visitor experience. These logs will automatically be purged after ninety (90) days.

## 3\. Control Panel Data Collection

ilait makes every practical effort to avoid excessive or irrelevant collection of Personal Data. We have implemented checks to alert you when entering information that might potentially be Personal Data in ilait Control Panel. If you believe ilait is collecting excessive information, we encourage you to contact us at privacy@ilait.com to raise any concerns.

ilait collect only information that is specifically and voluntarily provided by you. This means that you also have the ability to correct, amend, block or delete Personal Data directly via ilait Control Panel.

## 4\. Partner and Customer Accounts

An ilait Partner Account as well as any ilait Customer Account will have a primary contact person (first name, last name, email address and phone number). For Partner Accounts this information is mandatory to fulfill the Agreement. ilait will only use the provided Personal Data of this primary contact for internal contact requests. For external contact requests ilait will issue a Support Ticket informing the primary contact of the contact request. However, the primary contact can opt-in for public disclosure via ilait Control Panel. This enables ilait to provide external contact requestees with the primary contact information on file. 

All Partner Accounts will have one or more Administrators. An Administrator is a personal user account with administrative privileges for the Partner Account. All Personal Data collected for an Administrator will only be used to identify transactions, tracking actions and link them to an individual person. All newsletters, marketing and other communication can be disabled by the Administrator from the ilait Control Panel. Only email address and a display name are required. 

Partners can also assigned one or more Customer Administrators. An Customer Administrator is a personal user account with administrative privileges for a single Customer Account. All Personal Data collected for a Customer Administrator will only be used to identify transactions, tracking actions and link them to an individual person. No communication will be initiated to the Customer Administrator from ilait. Only email address and a display name are required.

ilait will not share Personal Data provided for an ilait Customer Account to any third party for marketing or communication purposes if not explicitly expressed in this Privacy Policy.

## 5\. Domain Name Registrations

ilait is an ICANN accredited registrar and provides domain registration services to partners and end customers. The data controller collecting Personal Data provided by you is the Domain Registry Operator, Domain Registrar (ilait) or Domain Sub-Registrar (ilait Partner) as set forth in DRA (Domain Registration Agreement). The Personal Data is collected to fulfill an agreement between you and ilait and/or the Domain Sub-Registrar. The Personal Data collected by ilait will be transferred to the respective Domain Registry Operator to fulfill the mentioned agreement.

By submitting Personal Data you provide the explicit consent to the use of the Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including any transborder transmission and/or data escrow necessary to fulfill the purpose of the data collected. Please see specific provisions for the top level domain registrar applicable to your registration. 

ilait will only use provided Personal Data for domain registration purposes. 

The Personal Data is only shared with the Domain Registry Operator when applicable. If there is an instance where such information need to be shared elsewhere, ilait will ask for permission beforehand. Note that the Domain Registry Operator and/or Domain Registrar will make your Personal Data public in the Registry Whois Database as set forth in DRA when applicable.

## 6\. Accuracy and Data Subject Rights

When ilait collects Personal Data, ilait assumes responsibility for keeping an accurate record of the information once submitted and verified. ilait does not assume responsibility for verifying the ongoing accuracy of the content of Personal Data. When practically possible, if ilait is informed that any Personal Data collected is no longer accurate, ilait will make appropriate corrections based on the updated information provided.

A Data Subject has the right to;

  * (i) full disclosure of Personal Data,
  * (ii) amend or delete Personal Data (as long as it will not interfere with the DPA requirements),
  * (iii) data portability, and
  * (iv) to file a complaint with the supervisory data protection authority.

A Data Subject should always contact the Partner in charge of the End Customer Account.

## 7\. Modifications

ilait reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time by publishing an updated version and you will be asked to accept when logging on to our services. The current version of the statement will be accessible on this website.

* * *

#### Revision 03/26/2018
